Finding Aid for Arvid Jouppi Papers, 1940-1987 (bulk 1963-1987)
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Writings
  - "Vaino Hoover Is A Man of Stature": no author (Box 24)